# KIRSTY FUREY

Wakefield, West Yorkshire

www.kirstyfurey.com

Telephone: <u>07500 337 515</u> | Email: <u>kirsty@kirstyfurey.com</u>

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kirsty-furey-071991105/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/kirsty-furey-071991105/</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/KirstyFurey">https://github.com/KirstyFurey</a>

Front End Developer | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Git | Debugging | Responsive design

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Looking to secure a Junior Front End Developer position to use and further develop my skills with HTML, CSS and JavaScript in a practical and fast-paced environment. I possess a meticulous eye for detail, a strong understanding of design, and extensive experience creating digital assets from briefs using the Adobe Creative Suite, gained during 10 years working in my current position. I use Codecademy, Front End Mentor, and Free Code Camp to further study, and work on personal projects in my spare time.

### **CORE SKILLS**

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Version control using Git & GitHub | Responsive design | Collaborative working | Debugging | Communication | Organisation | Leading a team | Adobe Dreamweaver | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe InDesign | Adobe Illustrator | Creating assets from brief | Detail oriented

#### **EDUCATION**

The Learning People - Front End Development - 2022

Leeds Arts University - BA(Hons) Photography - 2:1 - 2009

#### **PROJECTS**

Project title: Daniel Footwear Look Book

Brief description: Site showcasing the Daniel brand Autumn / Winter collection

https://danielfootwearlookbook.com/

Project title: e-Commerce Product Page

Brief description: Example of a product page for a trainers company with light-box, modals,

and editable shopping cart.

#### https://kirstyfurey.github.io/e-commerce-product-page/

Project title: Doodle Pairs

Brief description: JavaScript based matching pairs game

https://kirstyfurey.github.io/Doodle-Pairs/

Project title: Personal portfolio website

Brief description: My own portfolio website to showcase work and my personal brand

https://kirstyfurey.com/

## **WORK HISTORY**

### **Photography & Design Manager**

Daniel Footwear - 2012 to present

- Build Look Book website using HTML CSS & Javascript and create print version using InDesign.
- Implement changes to e-commerce site static HMTL pages.
- Manage photography and design workflow from delivery / brief to live on site.
- Work with marketing to organise and produce multi-channel photographic and digital assets for internal and external use in line with marketing and brand strategy.
- Ensure studio output exceeds industry standards and expectations.
- Continually assess and improve brand standards for photography, lighting, and design.
- Provide training to team members.
- Raise and troubleshoot any stock inaccuracies, working closely with merchandising and buying teams to resolve, ensuring 100% stock accuracy online.
- Ensure company targets and priorities for stock live on site are met by successful scheduling of Photography team and studio time.
- Ensure smooth studio workflow by continuous assessment of studio requirements and purchasing of equipment and consumables.
- Add value to company promotions by designing digital and print assets and managing ordering and delivery of physical assets and distribution to store locations.
- Multi-channel design, including email, homepage, social, and print in line with brand and marketing strategy.

#### Administration Manager

Michael Lewin Solicitors - 2009 to 2012

- Run the admin department and ensure department targets are met by managing hiring, training, workload, time and attendance, and holiday of the admin team within the company's Oakwood branch.
- Maintain efficiency of the office by dealing with external contractors and ordering supplies.
- Cultivate and maintain relationships with claims management companies in the tailoring of referral agreements and authorising invoices for payment.
- Maintaining, monitoring, and controlling the company's case management software and telephone systems internally.

· Onboarding new employees branch-wide.

# **Checkout General Assistant & Supervisor Support Runner**

Wm Morrisons PLC - 2003 to 2009

- Providing support to department manager in a supervisor support role, including running solo department open and closes, till corrections, and staff training.
- Maintain safe balance and distribute till change to checkouts.
- Run customer services counter resolving customer queries and complaints and providing company information, company policy details and assisting customers as needed.
- Complete customer's checkout at employee scanned, and self scan tills, resolving issues
  and ensuring the customer has a pleasant experience and leaves with a positive view of the
  company.

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

### **Digital Volunteer**

Manuel Bravo Project - 2020 to present

• Update and maintain Wordpress website